Guide to the Red Lodge Canning Company Records 1922-1974
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
Red Lodge Canning Company Records
1922-1974
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library The University of Montana, Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
Mss 101
Red Lodge Canning Company
66.25 linear feet 114 boxes and 5 oversize volumes
This collection contains Red Lodge Canning Company correspondence, financial, legal, organizational, promotional, photographic records as well as documents from the Rocky Mountain Distributing Company, a beer distribution division of the larger company.
Historical Note
In 1926, a group of investors organized the Red Lodge Canning Company in Red Lodge, Montana, and hired M.H. Mann as the manager. He became president of the company, and later the largest stockholder. His son, Blaine W. Mann, took over management of the company after M.H. retired.
The company operated canneries in Red Lodge and in Stevensville, Montana. Products canned included corn, peas, and beans from the Red Lodge and Stevensville, Montana areas. The company operated a beer distribution division, sometimes identified as Rocky Mountain Distributing Company, from 1950 to 1958. This division held distribution contracts with several brewing companies, local and national, for Carbon and Stillwater counties in Montana.
This collection contains Red Lodge Canning Company correspondence, financial, legal, organizational, promotional, photographic records as well as documents from the Rocky Mountain Distributing Company, a beer distribution division of the larger company. Aside from three folders of internal correspondence with the Stevensville operation and an extensive photographic sequence, all materials in this collection address the Red Lodge and Stevensville operations as one unit. The materials in this collection provide insights into Montana's rural canning industry, the extent of horticultural production in the state, horticultural product transportation/distribution networks, and the development of local food distribution economies through much of the 20th Century.
The collection is divided ito seven series:
Series I: Correspondence, 1924-1974, 58.25 linear feet
Subseries 1: General Correspondence
Subseries 2: Interoffice Correspondence
Series II: Financial, 1926-1969, 0.75 linear feet
Series III: Legal, 1926-1972, 0.75 linear feet
Series IV: Organization, 1926-1972, 1.0 linear feet
Series V: Printed Materials, 1922-1943, 0.75 linear feet
Series VI: Photographs, 1926, 73 images
Series VII: Beer Distributorship, 1950-1958, 2.25 linear feet
Subseries 1: General Correspondence
Subseries 2: Financial Records
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and the University of Montana-Missoula.
Blaine Mann originally gave the records to the Montana Historical Society.
Transferred from the Montana Historical Society, 1976.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Rocky Mountain Distributing Company
Red Lodge (Mont.)--Buildings, structures, etc. -- Photographs
Beer--Montana--Carbon County; Beer--Montana -- Stillwater County; Canneries--Montana--Red Lodge; Canneries--Montana -- Stevensville; Commercial buildings -- Montana--Red Lodge--Photographs; Distributors (Commerce) -- Montana--Carbon County; Distributors (Commerce) -- Montana--Stillwater County; Vegetables--Montana -- Red Lodge--Preservation; Vegetables--Montana -- Stevensville--Preservation
Business records -- Montana--Red Lodge; Business records -- Montana--Stevensville; Photographs--Montana -- Red Lodge
Montana; Photographs; Agriculture; Business, Industry, and Labor
- Correspondence, 1924-1974; Series I; 58.25 linear feet
  This series contains correspondence records from the Red Lodge Canning Company. Series materials are divided into two subseries, general and interoffice. The general correspondence subseries includes incoming and outgoing materials from company officials, primarily E.H. and Blaine Mann, to vegetable growers, canning suppliers, public officials, and distributors. These materials include exchanges with nearly every Montana Congressional representative during the time period, primarily concerning industry issues and company requests for special action. The interoffice subseries contains procedural memos and exchanges regarding leadership decisions.
  - General Correspondence, 1924-1974; Subseries 1; 56.0 linear feet
    - American Can Company, 1924 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - American Can Company, 1925 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Mann, M. H., 1925 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - A-Z, 1925 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - American Can Company of Utah, 1926 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - M. J. Boradori Company, 1926 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1926 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - A-B, 1926 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Calvert Lithographing Company, 1926 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Casey and Lanphier, 1926 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - C, 1926 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1926 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Farm Mortgage Company, 1926 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - D-F, 1926 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1926 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - J. R. Gentry Brokerage Company, 1926 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - G-H, 1926 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Kelley-Clarke Company, 1926 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Kohn Brothers Brokerage Company, 1926 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Lansing S. Warner Incorporated, 1926 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Leavitt and Eddington Company, 1926 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - I-L, 1926 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1926 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - L. P. Mason and Company, 1926 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1926 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Montana Board of Railroad Commissioners, 1926 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - M, 1926 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Northern Pacific Railroad, 1926 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1926 (Box-folder 3/8-9)
    - Charles H. Platter, 1926 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - N-R, 1926 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Scott Viner Company, 1926 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - R. A. Smith, 1926 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Sprague-Sells Corporation, 1926 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Stone-Hall Brokerage Company, 1926 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - S, 1926 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - T-V, 1926 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - V-Z, 1926 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Allen and Lewis, 1927 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - American Can Company, 1927 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - American Can Company of Utah, 1927 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Anaconda Copper Mining Company (Box-folder 5/3)
    - A, 1927 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Bismarck Grocery Company, 1927 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - M. J. Boradori Company, 1927 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1927 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - J. S. Brown Mercantile Company, 1927 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - B, 1927 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Calvert Lithographing Company, 1927 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Casey and Lanphier, 1927 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - C, 1927 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1927 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1927 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Epsten Lithographing Company, 1927 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - First National Bank of Butte, 1927 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - D-F, 1927 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - J. R. Gentry Brokerage Company, 1927 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - G, 1927 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Harwood Brokerage Company, 1927 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - H, 1927 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Kalispell Mercantile Company, 1927 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Keil Company, 1927 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Kohn Brothers Brokerage Company, 1927 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - I-K, 1927 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Lawrence Paper Manufacturing Company, 1927 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Leavitt Company, 1927 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Lewistown Mercantile Company, 1927 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Lindsey Company, Great Falls, Missoula, and Sheridan, Montana, 1927 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Logan Brokerage Company, 1927 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - L, 1927 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - McCord Brady Company, 1927 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Meinrath Corbaley, 1927 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Continued, 1927 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Meyer and Chapman State Bank, 1927 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Midland Canning Company, 1927 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Miles City Mercantile Company, 1927 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Montana, 1927 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Montana Board of Railroad Commissioners, 1927 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - Montana National Bank, 1927 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - M, 1927 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Nash-Finch Company, 1927 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - National Park Bank, 1927 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Nelson Steamship Company, 1927 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - J. H. Newbauer and Company, 1927 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Nivison-Weiskopf Company, 1927 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Northern Grocery Company, 1927 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Northern Pacific Railway Company, 1927 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - No-Vary Products Company, 1927 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - N, 1927 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Scott Wholesale Grocery Company Incorporated, 1927 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1927 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1927 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1927 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1927 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1927 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1927 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1927 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Charles H. Platter, 1927 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - O-Q, 1927 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Ryan Grocery Company, 1927 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Ryan-Sheridan Company, 1927 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - R, 1927 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Scott Viner Company, 1927 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Sprague-Sells Corporation, 1927 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Staunton Wholesale Company, 1927 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Stone Hall Brokerage, 1927 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Stone Ordean Wells Company, 1927 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - S, 1927 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - U.S. National Bank, 1927 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - U.S. Printing and Lithograph Company, 1927 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - T-V, 1927 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Western States Grocery Company, 1927 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Western Wholesale Grocery Company, 1927 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Winston-Newell Company, 1927 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Wyoming Grocery Company, 1927 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - W, 1927 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - X-Z, 1927 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - American Can Company, 1927 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Anaconda Copper Mining Company, 1927 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - E. B. Andrus Grocery Company, 1927 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - A, 1928 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1928 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Bismarck Grocery Company, 1928 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Boradori Company, 1928 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1928 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Bristol Gustafson Brokerage Company, 1928 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - J. S. Brown Mercantile Company, 1928 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - B, 1928 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Calvert Lithographing Company, 1928 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - C, 1928 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Farmers State Bank, 1928 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - D-F, 1928 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - G-J, 1928 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Keil Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Kohn Brothers Brokerage Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Lindsay Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Logan Brokerage Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1928 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Midland Canning Company, 1928 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Miles City Mercantile, 1928 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Montana, 1928 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - K-M, 1928 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1928 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Nelson Steamship Company, 1928 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Nivison-Weiskopf Company, 1928 (Box-folder 14/7)
    - No-Vary Products, 1928 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Edward Olcott Company, 1928 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1928 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1928 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1928 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1928 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - N-O, 1928 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - P-Q, 1928 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Ryan Grocery Company, 1928 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Ryan Mercantile Company, 1928 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Ryan-Sheridan Company, 1928 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - R, 1928 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Scott Viner Company, 1928 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Sprague-Sells Corporation, 1928 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Stone Hall Brokerage Company, 1928 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Stone-Ordean-Wells Company, 1928 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - S, 1928 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - T, 1928 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - U.S. National Bank of Red Lodge, 1928 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - U, 1928 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Winston-Newell, 1928 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - W-Z, 1928 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - American Can Company, 1929 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Ariss, Campbell and Gault, 1929 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1929 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1929 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - T. S. Brown Mercantile Company, 1929 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - A-B, 1929 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - The Calvert Lithographing Company, 1929 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Carpenter Paper Company, 1929 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Earl V. Cline, 1929 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - C-D, 1929 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1929 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1929 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - E-G, 1929 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Lindsay, Helena, 1929 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - H-L, 1929 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1929 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Meinrath Corbaly Company, 1929 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Meinrath Corbaly Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Midland Canning Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Miles City Mercantile Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Montana State Board of Railroad Commissioners, 1929 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Montana, 1929 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Morey Mercantile Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/8)
    - National Bag Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - No-Vary Products, 1929 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1929 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1929 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Paine Weber and Company, 1929 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - M-Q, 1929 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Ryan Grocery Company, 1929 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - R, 1929 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Stone Hall Brokerage Company, 1929 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Stone-Ordean-Wells Company, 1929 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - S-V, 1929 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Wood, Sterling, 1929 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - W-Z, 1929 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - American Can Company, 1930 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Ariss Campbell and Gault, 1930 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Bellrose and Holliday, 1930 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Billings Hardware Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Billings Traffic Bureau, 1930 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Bismarck Grocery Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Brotherton-Kirk Seed Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - A-B, 1930 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Calvert Lithographing, 1930 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Carpenter Paper Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Casey Lanphier Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - C, 1930 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1930 (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1930 (Box-folder 20/15)
    - D-G, 1930 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Hansen Canning Machinery Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Keil Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Kohn Brothers Brokerage Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/5)
    - H-L, 1930 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Matchett Macklem Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1930 (Box-folder 21/10)
    - Midland Canning Company, 1930 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Miles City Mercantile, 1930 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Montana, 1930 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1930 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Northern Pacific Railroad, 1930 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - No-Vary Products, 1930 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1930 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1930 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - M-O, 1930 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Red and White Corporation, 1930 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Ryan Grocery Company, 1930 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Stockholders, 1930 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Stone Hall Brokerage Company, 1930 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Stone-Ordean Wells, 1930 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - P-S, 1930 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - U.S. Forest Service, 1930 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Wadhams and Company, 1930 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - West Coast Grocery Company, 1930 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Company, 1930 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Wisconsin Brokerage Company, 1930 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - T-Z, 1930 (Box-folder 23/11)
    - American Can Company, 1931 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1931 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Bismarck Grocery Company, 1931 (Box-folder 23/14)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1931 (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Bristol Gustafson Brokerage Company, 1931 (Box-folder 23/16)
    - A-B, 1931 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Casey and Lanphier, 1931 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Casey and Lanphier, 1931 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - C, 1931 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1931 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1931 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1931 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Huntley Manufacturing Company, 1931 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Keil Company, 1931 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Kelly Clarke Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Kohn Brothers Brokerage Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - James Q. Leavitt, 1931 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Lindsay Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - D-L, 1931 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Matchett Macklem Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1931 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1931 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Midland Canning Company, 1931 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Miles City Mercantile, 1931 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Montana, 1931 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1931 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - No-Vary Products, 1931 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1931 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1931 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - M-O, 1931 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Red and White Corporation, 1931 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Ryan Grocery Company, 1931 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - P-R, 1931 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Stone-Hall Brokerage, 1931 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Stone Ordean Wells, 1931 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - S-Z, 1931 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Ahda Wagan Paper Product Company, 1932 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - American Can Company, 1932 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Associated Seed Growers Incorporated, 1932 (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1932 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Bismarck Grocery Company, 1932 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1932 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Casey and Lanphier, 1932 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Casey and Lanphier, 1932 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Chislhom Ryder Company, 1932 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - A-C, 1932 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1932 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - John M. Evans, 1932 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1932 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Rollo Gillikson, 1932 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Hotel Winton, 1932 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - James Fenwick Company, 1932 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - James Fenwick Company, 1932 (Box-folder 28/11)
    - D-H, 1932 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Jones-Moor Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Alfred P. Martin Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Matchett Macklem Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1932 (Box-folder 29/10)
    - Midland Canning Company, 1932 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Miles City Mercantile, 1932 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Montana, 1932 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Morrison Brothers Seed Company, 1932 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - I-M, 1932 (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1932 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - The Nitragin Company, 1932 (Box-folder 30/7)
    - N, 1932 (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1932 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Red and White Corporation, 1932 (Box-folder 30/10)
    - E. J. Rinaud Company, 1932 (Box-folder 30/11)
    - Ryan Grocery Co, 1932 (Box-folder 30/12)
    - O-R, 1932 (Box-folder 30/13)
    - Stone-Hall Brokerage Company, 1932 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Stone-Ordean-Wells Company, 1932 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - S, 1932 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - United States, 1932 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Thomas J. Walsh, 1932 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Burton K. Wheeler, 1932 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - T-Z, 1932 (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Ahdawagam Paper Product Company, 1933 (Box-folder 31/8)
    - American Can Company, 1933 (Box-folder 31/9)
    - Bismarck Grocery Company, 1933 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - Bozeman Canning Company, 1933 (Box-folder 31/11)
    - A-B, 1933 (Box-folder 31/12)
    - Casey-Lanphier Company, 1933 (Box-folder 31/13)
    - T. J. Lanphier Company, 1933 (Box-folder 31/14)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1933 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1933 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - James Fenwick Company, 1933 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - C-F, 1933 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1933 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - G-L, 1933 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1933 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Alfred P. Martin Company, 1933 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Matchett Macklem Company, 1933 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1933 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1933 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Montana, 1933 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1933 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - National Canners Association, 1933 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - M-N, 1933 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Montana, 1933 (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Red and White Corporation, 1933 (Box-folder 33/9)
    - F. X. Schilling, 1933 (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Sprague-Sells Corporation, 1933 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Stone-Hall Brokerage Company, 1933 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - O-T, 1933 (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Wadhams and Company, 1933 (Box-folder 34/5)
    - U-Z, 1933 (Box-folder 34/6)
    - American Can Company, 1934 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - John J. Ehlinger Company, 1934 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - A-E, 1934 (Box-folder 34/9)
    - F-G, 1934 (Box-folder 34/10)
    - T. J. Lanphier Company, 1934 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - T. J. Lanphier Company, 1934 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - H-L, 1934 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1934 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Meinrath Corbaley Company, 1934 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Montana, 1934 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Nash-Finch Company, 1934 (Box-folder 35/7)
    - National Canners Association, 1934 (Box-folder 35/8)
    - M-R, 1934 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - S-Z, 1934 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - A-Z, 1937 (Box-folder 36/3)